(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-11T10:16:27.674681",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから 一人じゃないから
because your pieces are in this heart, because I'm not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Within the words we once drew,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
the coloring scenery swayed beyond closed eyes.
少し戸惑う風の中
In the slightly hesitating wind,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
overlapping petals, our voices.
一瞬間 瞬間 捕らえるみたいに
As if capturing every single moment,
もっと もっと もっと 踏み出せたら 【we are one】
if we could step forward more and more... 【we are one】
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
because your pieces are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather today's light
僕と集め 空に放つ
and release it into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから 力が湧くから
We'll gently make this miracle shine together, because strength wells up within.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clutching new seeds tightly,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
I sowed them with a strong wish toward the distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the wind of hope blow,
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
ideal petals, praying for tomorrow's sky.
何百億も光る星みたいに ずっとずっとずっと終わらないから
Like hundreds of millions of shining stars, never ever ending,
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめ 今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
this smile will embrace the past and reach out to the future now.
時には転んでいても 空を見上げよう 笑い日々を刻んでゆく
Even when stumbling, let's look up at the sky and carve out smiling days.
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから 踏み出そうここから
Promising to grasp the next dream, let's take a step forward from here.
同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手にしたい
We want to see the same future, make that dream our own.
触れた奇跡の中で その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
In the touched miracle, if we blend into the sky extending beyond,
君の場所と今をつなげたくて
wanting to connect your place and the present.
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
because your pieces are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を 僕と集め 空に放つ
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather today's light and release it into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから 咲かせようここから 一緒に
We'll gently make this miracle shine together, let's make it bloom from here together.
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
because your pieces are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather today's light
僕と集め 空に放つ
and release it into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから 咲かせようここから 一緒に 一人じゃないから 【we are one】
We'll gently make this miracle shine together, let's make it bloom from here together, because we are not alone 【we are one】.
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
because your pieces are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を 僕と集め 空に放つ
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather today's light and release it into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから 咲かせようここから 一緒に
We'll gently make this miracle shine together, let's make it bloom from here together.
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
because your pieces are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を 僕と集め 空に放つ
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather today's light and release it into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから 咲かせようここから 一緒に
We'll gently make this miracle shine together, let's make it bloom from here together.
一人じゃないから
We are one.
バンダイ バンダイスピリッツより
From Bandai and Bandai Spirits,
EXPO会場でも展示中の商品をご紹介！
introducing products on display at the EXPO venue!
たくさんの商品が発売いたします！
Many products will be released!
「ロボ子さん」がRelax timeで登場予定！
"Roboco-san" is scheduled to appear in Relax time!
一番くじ ホロライブ アートアクリルコレクション
Ichiban Kuji Hololive Art Acrylic Collection
会場限定でプレゼント！バンダイ/バンダイスピリッツブースでは会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
Venue-limited gift! Venue-limited goods are also distributed for free at the Bandai / Bandai Spirits booth!
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえる！
You can also get a coupon on Pre-Ban that you can use right away!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも征服しよ？
Shall we conquer the Weiss Schwarz stage too?
楽しもう！
Let's enjoy it!
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション サマーコレクション 3月22日(金)発売！
Premium Booster Hololive Production Summer Collection releases Friday, March 22nd!
ホロスターズが
HOLOSTARS is
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
appearing in Weiss Schwarz Blau!
ようこそカードゲームの舞台へ！
Welcome to the card game stage!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ スタートデッキ&ブースターパック
Weiss Schwarz Blau Start Deck & Booster Pack
hololive SUPER EXPO 2024 開催を記念してホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが新衣装になって再登場！
To commemorate hololive SUPER EXPO 2024, Hololive members' Nendoroids reappear in new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどをお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids!
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に
FuRyu's "Hololive" prizes are coming to amusement facilities nationwide!
2024年7月以降に続々登場！
Appearing one after another starting July 2024!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
Scheduled to be rolled out for all domestic Hololive members in the future!
彼女たちと一緒に夢をつめこんだ 胸がときめく新たなブランド
A heart-pounding new brand packed with dreams together with them...
あの涙が今の僕らをつなげて
Those tears connect us right now...
この心に君のカケラがあるから 一人じゃないから
Your pieces are in my heart, so I'm not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Within the letters I once drew,
目を閉じた先につむぐ景色が揺れた
the scenery trembled beyond my closed eyes.
少し戸惑う風の中 (響く)
Amidst a slightly hesitating wind (resounding),
重なる花びら 私たちの声
overlapping flower petals, our voices.
一瞬 (一瞬) 一瞬 (一瞬) 捕らえるみたいに
Capture every single moment, as if to seize it.
もっと (もっと) もっと 踏み出せたら 【we are one】
Taking that step forward and more... [We are one]
あの涙が今の僕らをつなげて (つなげて)
Those tears connect us right now (connect us),
この心に君のカケラがあるから
Your pieces are in my heart, so I'm not alone.
強くなくてもいい (なくてもいい) 今の光を
It's okay not to be strong (it's okay), gathering today's light
僕と (君と) 集め (すべて) 空に放つ
with you (with you), collecting (everything) to release into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから (その手で) 力が湧くから
We'll make this miracle gently shine together (with our hands), because strength wells up.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clutching new seeds,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
I scattered them with strong wishes toward a distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては (泳ぐ)
Fostering the winds of hope (swimming),
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
ideal flower petals, praying for tomorrow's sky.
何百 (何百) 億も (億も) 光る星みたいに
Like hundreds of millions of shining stars,
ずっと (ずっと) ずっと終わらないから
because it will go on forever and ever.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて (抱きしめて)
These smiles strongly embrace the past (embrace them),
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
reaching out to the future now.
時に転んでも (それでいい) 空を見上げよう
Even if we tumble sometimes (that's fine), let's look up at the sky.
笑い (泣いた) 日々を (すべて) 刻んでゆく
Engraving days of laughter (and tears) (everything),
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから (この手で) 踏み出そう ここから
promising to seize the next dream (with this hands), let's step out from here.
(we are with you we are with you)
同じ未来を見たい あの夢手にしたい
Wanting to see the same future, wanting to make that dream ours.
(we are with you capture the moment) 触れた奇跡の中で
(We are with you, capture the moment) Amidst the touched miracle,
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
if we are woven into the sky extending beyond,
君の場所と今をつなげたくて
wanting to connect your place and now.
あの涙が今の僕らをつなげて (つなげて)
Those tears connect us right now (connect us),
この心に君のカケラがあるから
Your pieces are in my heart, so I'm not alone.
強くなくてもいい (なくてもいい) 今の光を
It's okay not to be strong (it's okay), gathering today's light
僕と (君と) 集め (すべて) 空に放つ
with you (with you), collecting (everything) to release into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから (この手で)
We'll make this miracle gently shine with us (with this hands),
咲かせよう ここから (一緒に)
let's make them bloom from here (together),
一人じゃないから 【we are one】
because we are not alone. [We are one]
I will continue to support you!
Saya akan terus mendukung Anda!
by Oharaihorma
5th fes. 初めて参加します！
ライブ楽しみにしてます！
(♪ Instrumental music playing)
初壇地！全力でめいっぱい応援します！
ホロライブ5th fes. おめでとうございます！
hololive 5th fes.最高に楽しんでください！
Can't wait to see cute idol on stage since last year.
I can't wait to see cute idol on stage since last year.
Let's Capture the MODMOMENT!
by hooman funclub
Ina, I'm really looking forward to seeing you during holofes!
Have a lot of fun! Edu Lima
I'm so happy to finally see all my oshis on stage, you're gonna rock it! :D/ Edu Lima
Cheers to all the talents! Hope you all have fun in these two days! AllStar!
WISH EVERYONE THE BEST and have fun out there! CHEERS! - AllStar!
I can't wait to see your performance on stage! Do your best, IRyS!! - ErikBaThe
この時を待ってました！いにづいにライブはもちろん、
2日間の開催期間も全力で楽しませていただきます！
全力で楽しんでいきましょう！
Capture the Moment!
今日という日を大切にしたい！最高のステージにできますように！
Krona!! Your journey is an inspiration to us. Stay strong and keep creating beautiful moment! 아르티스
Hope it's a fantastic performance! Always cheering for you, Kronii! - Sword Ark
(♪ Instrumental music playing)
バンダイ、バンダイスピリッツより、EXPO会場でも展示中の商品をご紹介！
Introducing products on display at the EXPO venue from Bandai and Bandai Spirits!
ウエハースや一番くじなど、たくさんの商品が発売いたします！
Wafers, Ichiban Kuji, and many other products will be released!
ぜひチェックしてくださいね！
Be sure to check them out!
バンダイブース、バンダイスピリッツブースでは
At the Bandai Booth and Bandai Spirits Booth,
会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
venue-limited goods are also being given away for free!
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえるチャンス！
A chance to get a coupon you can use right away on Premium Bandai!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
楽しむ準備はいい？
Ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも青春しよう！
Let's have youth on the Weiß Schwarz stage too!
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション サマーコレクション 3月22日(金)発売
Premium Booster Hololive Production Summer Collection Releasing Friday, March 22nd
ホロスターズがヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
HOLOSTARS makes its debut in Weiß Schwarz Blau!
ようこそカードゲームの舞台へ！
Welcome to the card game stage!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ スタートデッキ&ブースターパック 好評発売中
Weiß Schwarz Blau Start Deck & Booster Pack now on sale
ホロライブSUPER EXPO 2024開催を記念して、ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが新衣装になって再登場！
Commemorating hololive SUPER EXPO 2024, hololive members' Nendoroids reappear in new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどをお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids!
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に
Hololive prizes from Furyu are coming to amusement facilities nationwide
2024年7月以降に続々登場！
appearing one after another starting July 2024!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
Planned for rollout for all domestic hololive members in the future!
最新情報はキャラ広場で検索
Search Chara-Hiroba for the latest info
推しの曲 めっちゃいいね！
Your oshi's songs are so good!
みるハコチャンス！
Miruhako Chance!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your oshi's content with full presence!
音も推そう！みるハコ！
Support your oshi with sound too! Miruhako!
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君の欠片がいるから
Because fragments of you are in this heart,
一人じゃないから
Because I'm not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Inside the words we drew someday,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
The scenery that colored beyond closed eyes swayed.
少し戸惑う風の中 (響く)
In the slightly hesitant wind (echoing),
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping petals, our voices.
一瞬 一瞬
Moment by moment,
捕らえるみたいに
as if to capture them,
もっと もっと
more and more,
もっと踏み出せたら 【we are one】
if we could step forward more... [we are one].
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now...
この心に君の欠片がいるから
Because fragments of you are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong...
今の光を僕と君と集めすべて空に放つ
Gathering our light, we release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせれるから
Because we can gently make this miracle shine together.
力が湧くから
Because power wells up from within.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clenching new seeds tightly,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
I scattered them with strong prayers toward a distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the wind of hope blow through,
理想の花びら祈る明日の空
ideal petals pray for tomorrow's sky.
何百 何百 億も 億も
Hundreds of millions,
光る星みたいに
like shining stars,
ずーっと ずーっと
always, always,
ずーっと終わらないから
it will never end.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile embraces the past firmly,
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
reaching out this hand toward the future.
時に転んででも
Even if we stumble sometimes,
空を見上げようよ
let's look up at the sky.
笑い(泣いた)日日を(すべて)刻んでゆく
Carving out all the smiling and crying days,
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから(この手で)踏み出そうここから
promising to grasp the next dream together.
踏み出そう ここから
Let's step forward from here.
we are with you
同じ未来を見 ていたい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to make that dream my own.
we are with you , capture the moment
We are with you, capture the moment.
触れた奇跡の中で
Amidst the touched miracle,
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
if caught in the sky extending beyond,
君の場所と今をつなぎたくて
I want to connect your place and the present.
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now...
この心に君の欠片がいるから
Because fragments of you are in this heart.
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong...
今の光を僕と君と集めすべて空に放つ
Gathering our light, we release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせれるから
Because we can gently make this miracle shine together.
咲かせよう ここから (一緒に)
Let's make it bloom from here, together.
一人じゃないから 【we are one】
Because we are not alone [we are one].
Capture the moment...
Capture the moment
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから
because fragments of you live in this heart.
一人じゃないから
We are not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Within the words we once drew,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
the colors swayed beyond closed eyes.
少し戸惑う風の中
In the slightly hesitant wind,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
overlapping petals, our voices resonate.
一瞬 一瞬 捕らえるみたいに
As if capturing every single moment,
もっと もっと もっと 踏み出したなら
if we take another step forward—
【 we are one 】
We are one!
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから
because fragments of you live in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay if you're not strong, let's gather
僕と君に集め 空に放つ
today's light with you and release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせ るから 力が湧くから
We'll make this miracle gently shine, because it gives us strength.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clasping a new seed in our hands,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
we sowed it with strong hopes for a distant future.
希望の風を吹かせには
Letting the wind of hope blow—
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
ideal petals praying for tomorrow's sky.
何百 何億も光る星みたいに
Like hundreds of millions of shining stars,
ずっと ずっと ずっと終わらないから
it will go on forever and ever.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile tightly embraces the past,
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
reaching out this hand toward the future now.
時に転んでも空を見上げよう
Even if we stumble sometimes, let's look up at the sky,
笑い泣いた日々を刻んでゆく
carving out the days we laughed and cried.
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから
Promising to grasp our next dream—
踏み出そうここから
let's take a step forward from here!
同じ未来を見ていたいいあの夢手にした い
Wanting to see the same future, wanting to make that dream ours—
触れた奇跡の中で その先まで続く空にまぎれなら
drifting into the sky extending beyond the miracle we touched,
君の場所と今をつなげたくて
wanting to connect your place with the present.
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから
because fragments of you live in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay if you're not strong, let's gather
僕と君に集め 空に放つ
today's light with you and release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせ るから 咲かせようここから
We'll make this miracle gently shine—let's make it bloom from here!
一緒に
Together,
一人じゃないから
because we are not alone
【 we are one 】
We are one!
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから
because fragments of you live in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay if you're not strong, let's gather
僕と君に集め 空に放つ
today's light with you and release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせ るから (この手で)
We'll make this miracle gently shine with these hands,
咲かせようここから (一緒に)
let's make it bloom from here together!
一人じゃないから 【 we are one 】
because we are not alone—we are one!
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから
because fragments of you live in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay if you're not strong, let's gather
僕と君に集め 空に放つ
today's light with you and release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせ るから (この手で)
We'll make this miracle gently shine with these hands,
咲かせようここから (一緒に)
let's make it bloom from here together!
一人じゃないから 【 we are one 】
because we are not alone—we are one!
あの涙が 今の僕らをつなげて
That tear connects us right now,
この心に 君のカケラがあるから
because fragments of you reside in this heart.
一人じゃないから
Because we are not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Within the letters I drew one day,
目を閉じた先に 色づく景色が揺れた
beyond closed eyes, a colorful landscape swayed.
少し戸惑う 風の中
In the slightly bewildered wind,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
overlapping petals become our voices.
一瞬 一瞬
Just like capturing
捕まえるみたいに
every single moment,
もっと もっと
if we can take
もっと踏み出せたら
one more step forward—
あの涙が 今の僕らをつなげて
That tear connects us right now,
この心に 君のカケラがあるから
because fragments of you reside in this heart.
強くなってもいい
It's okay even if we're not strong,
今の光を
gathering today's light
僕と 集め
with you and me,
空に放つ
and releasing it to the sky.
この奇跡を 僕らで そっと輝かせるから
We'll make this miracle gently shine together,
力が湧くから
because strength wells up from within.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clasping new seeds tightly,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め蒔いた
I sowed them with a strong wish for the distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the wind of hope blow,
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
ideal petals pray for tomorrow's sky.
何百 億も
Like hundreds of millions
光る星みたいに
of shining stars,
ずっと ずっと
it will never,
ずっと終わらないから
ever end.
この笑顔が 過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile tightly embraces the past,
今 未来に この手伸ばしてゆくから
as I now reach out this hand toward the future.
時に転んでもいい
It's okay to stumble sometimes,
空を見上げよう
let's look up at the sky.
笑い 日々を
Etching all the days
刻んでゆく
we laughed and cried,
次の夢を掴み取るって 約束するから
I promise we'll seize our next dream together,
踏み出そう ここから
let's take a step forward from here.
同じ未来を見 ていたい
We want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
we want to hold that dream in our hands.
触れた奇跡の中で
Within the miracle we touched—
その先まで続く 空にまぎれたら
If we blend into the sky extending beyond,
君の場所と今をつなげたくて
I want to connect your place with right now.
あの涙が 今の僕らをつなげて
That tear connects us right now,
この心に 君のカケラがあるから
because fragments of you reside in this heart.
強くなってもいい
It's okay even if we're not strong,
今の光を
gathering today's light
僕と 集め
with you and me,
空に放つ
and releasing it to the sky.
この奇跡を 僕らで そっと輝かせるから
We'll make this miracle gently shine together,
咲かせよう ここから
let's make it bloom from here.
一人じゃないから
Because we are not alone.
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
湊あくあ
Minato Aqua
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
AZKi
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
猫又おかゆ
Nekomata Okayu
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
ワトソン・アメリア
Watson Amelia
セレス・ファウナ
Ceres Fauna
七詩ムメイ
Nanashi Mumei
目覚めたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our freshly awakened heartbeats resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time, with the best friends
きらめきに戻って
Returning to the sparkle
思い出から 大切の歌
From memories, a song of preciousness
懐かしいね
It's nostalgic, isn't it?
私の声が届いていくよ
My voice is reaching out
もう少し
Just a little bit more
あの日から続く未来は今
The future continuing from that day is right now
皆と掴んだ今日だよ
The day we grasped together with everyone
もっともっともっともっと加速する未来を
An accelerating future, more and more and more
届いてかなえたいから
Because I want to reach and make it come true
行くよどこまでも
I'll go anywhere
旅立ちの準備はOK
Preparation for the journey is OK
ひらけ夢の扉を
Open the door of dreams
いつだってきらめきの中へ
Always into the sparkle
目覚めたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our freshly awakened heartbeats resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to meet you
みんなで歌おう
Let's sing together
終わらないメロディ きらめきに戻って
An endless melody, returning to the sparkle
届いてかなえたいから 私の声で
Because I want to reach and make it come true with my voice
届けたいのは君に笑顔を
What I want to deliver to you is a smile
微笑んで 一歩を
Smiling steps
一歩ずつ 大人になっても悔やしくて
Step by step, even if I regret it when I become an adult
皆の温もりはいつまでも
Everyone's warmth is forever
手を上げて
Raise your hands.
clap your hands 海の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sea,
clap your hands 届き ますように
may the claps reach you.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
ほら 一緒に everybody
C'mon now, together with everybody!
clap your hands 空の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sky,
clap your hands 響きますように
may the claps resound.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
光射す 僕たちの未来
Light shines upon our future.
始まりましょうか さあ diving
Shall we start? C'mon, let's dive into it.
待っても意味ない timing
There's no use in waiting, it's not a matter of timing.
あの魚みたいに swimming swimming
Like those fishes, swimming, swimming.
引き寄せるの lighting
The lighting attracts us,
まだ見えないよ maybe
maybe you still can't see it yet.
この先には何があるの?
What lies ahead of us?
まだ早いよ take it
It's still early so just take it.
追いつくまで shaking
I'm shaking until we catch up.
でもたまに止まって thinking thinking
But sometimes, we gotta stop and think, think.
変えてみせて change
I'll try changing things,
踏み出すのさ stepping
taking a step forward, stepping.
掴んでみるよ キラめき my dream
I'll try grasping my sparkling dream.
叶える日 まで story 繋ぐから
Connecting the story until the day it comes true,
だって 君 に ずっと 見て ほしい から
because I want you to gaze at me always.
手を上げて
Raise your hands.
clap your hands 海の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sea,
clap your hands 届き ますように
may the claps reach you.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
ほら 一緒に everybody
C'mon now, together with everybody!
clap your hands 空の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sky,
clap your hands 響きますように
may the claps resound.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
光射す 僕たちの未来
Light shines upon our future.
今日 はいらない breaking
Today, no need for breaking,
理性 壊せ breaking
breaking down reason.
何時でも いい でしょう 四六時中
Anytime is fine, twenty-four seven.
君 は 何 を feeling
What are you feeling?
解き放て sparking
Unleash the sparking,
暗闇 に 放つ レーザービーム
releasing a laser beam into the darkness.
光らせ て stage 作る から
Illuminating the stage because we're creating it,
だって 君 に もっと 見て ほしい から
because I want you to gaze at me even more.
手を上げて
Raise your hands.
clap your hands 海の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sea,
clap your hands 届き ますように
may the claps reach you.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
ほら 一緒に everybody
C'mon now, together with everybody!
clap your hands 空の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sky,
clap your hands 響きますように
may the claps resound.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
重なる wave 世界 を 揺らせ
Let overlapping waves shake the world!
終わり が ある こと くらい すでに i know
I know that everything has an end,
でも まだまだ 泳ぎ 足りない の
but I still haven't had enough of swimming.
君 crazy
You're crazy,
まるで lazy
you're practically lazy,
次元 混ざり 合う の すべて 塗り替える blue
dimensions mixing together, repainting everything blue.
手を上げて
Raise your hands.
clap your hands 海の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sea,
clap your hands 届き ますように
may the claps reach you.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
ほら 一緒に everybody
C'mon now, together with everybody!
clap your hands 空の向こう までに
Clap your hands across the sky,
clap your hands 響きますように
may the claps resound.
手を叩こう 手を開こう
Let's clap our hands, let's open our hands!
光射す 僕たちの未来
Light shines upon our future.
生意気に魔が刺したなんて
Saying a wicked thought just crossed my mind—
チンデな成り行きではないんだよ
it's not just some cheap, ordinary turn of events.
地獄の沙汰を変えたくて
Wanting to change the judgment of hell,
抜かりなく懐(ふところ)入れたマイボーイ
my boy, we slipped right in without a slip-up.
浮気性な回りものは
Fickle and spinning things—
ちょっとずぶいくらいが好きらしい
it seems we like them a bit sloppy.
一度味わえば戻れない
Once you taste it, you can't go back;
やけにイージーで戸惑うくらい
it's so strangely easy it leaves you bewildered.
いい眺めだろう
Quite a view, isn't it?
カリスマだろう
Quite charismatic, isn't it?
陶酔してのぼせきってその先は?
Intoxicated and dizzy, what lies beyond that?
堪んないマネー
Unbearable money,
ダーティー ダーティーなマネー
dirty, dirty money.
病みつきになっていくイルな狂躁
An ill frenzy that turns into an addiction.
堪んないマネーもっともっとじっくり
Unbearable money, more and more, carefully—
嘘も真にしてギミミニ
turning lies into truth, gimimini!
ギミギミ もっと ほら
Give me, give me more, c'mon—
ギミギミ もっと
give me, give me more!
この心を潤してくれ
Soothe this heart of mine.
ギミギミ もっと
Give me, give me more!
埋まらないがらくたのように
Like untamable junk,
この心を潤してくれ
soothe this heart of mine.
遠慮せずお好きなように
Don't hold back, have it just the way you like;
プラテポルテ端から端まで
ready-to-wear from edge to edge.
簡易だね呆れるくらい
It's so simple it's appalling,
張り付いた笑顔も現金で
even plastered smiles traded for cash.
でも明日は? 数秒後には?
But tomorrow? Seconds from now?
焦燥感に殺されそうな夜は飲み込んで
Swallow down the nights about to be killed by impatience.
さぞ楽だろう まぁ続くだろう
Must be quite easy, well, it'll go on—
慰めて…アバンチュールはお幾らで?
console me... how much is an adventure?
たまらないハニー
Irresistible honey,
ビューティ ビューティなハニー
beauty, beautiful honey.
病みつきになっていく奢奢なパーティナイト
A lavish party night turning into an addiction.
たまらないハニーもっともっとじっくりねぎらって
Irresistible honey, more and more, carefully pamper me—
フルコースでラブ ミー ハニー
with a full course, love me honey!
たまらないマネー
Irresistible money,
もしかして やっぱり
could it be, as expected,
一歩 間違えりゃ なわしゅ lose out
if you make one wrong step, you'll lose out.
「なあ、全部だめになってもそばにいてくれよ I believe buddy」
"Hey, even if everything falls apart, stay by my side, I believe buddy."
ギミギミ もっと
Give me, give me more!
じりじり burn out
Slowly burning out,
この心を潤してくれ
soothe this heart of mine.
あけすけな反応
Outspoken reaction,
埋まらないがらくたのように
like untamable junk—
この心を潤してくれ
soothe this heart of mine.
ギミギミ もっと
Give me, give me more!
じりじり burn out
Slowly burning out,
この心を潤してくれ
soothe this heart of mine.
ギミギミ もっと ラブ ミー ラブ ミー 本気
Give me, give me more, love me, love me for real—
この心を潤してくれ
soothe this heart of mine.
誰でもいい
Anyone is fine,
抱き締めてくれ！
just hold me tight!
駆け込んでくギリギリだ
Rushing in right at the wire
“閉まる扉ご注意を” 深呼吸
“Mind the closing doors,” take a deep breath
ツベコベ言わず......Right now!
No complaints, just... Right now!
大気圏突入のイメージトレーニング
Mental training for atmospheric entry
揺れる感情 じれったい欲望みたいだ
Shaking emotions, like frustrating desires
嫌いな人にお別れを
Say goodbye to the people you hate
もう二度とは会えない 戻らないさ
You'll never see them again, there's no turning back
もっと歪んで Distortion
Distortion, twisting even more
うざいね Destruction
Annoying, Destruction
そう終わりだ Destination......
That's the end, Destination...
行こう何光年先の果ての世界へ
Let's go to a world at the edge, light-years away
飛ばしてく 過剰に暴れたいね
Flying forward, wanting to rage excessively
くらおうさく響いたルール破って
Take that, breaking the loudly echoing rules
Double up かかって来いと笑うさ
Double up, I just smile and tell you to bring it on
四六時中 抱き合って あの惑星が消えるまで
Hugging each other 24/7 until that planet disappears
無重力サカサマ
Zero-gravity, upside-down
五線譜はみ出す lazy で tricky な trip さ
A lazy and tricky trip overflowing the staff
激しく奏でる月のレクイエム
A violently playing requiem of the moon
荷物などとうに捨てた 切符一つで
I discarded my luggage long ago, with just a single ticket
片道の non stop から“Utopia”
From a one-way non-stop to "Utopia"
鳴らし本能覚醒をここで証明しよう
Ring out, let's prove the awakening of instinct here
ブチあげる 不滅に 狂いたいね
Blow it up, immortal, I want to go crazy
つかみ怖いぐらいの衝撃 アタック脳天さ
Grab the terrifying impact, an attack straight to the head
Double up まだまだやれる なんてね
Double up, we can still do more, or so I say
五里霧中 動けないよ この星雲を泳ぎ切って
Lost in a thick fog, unable to move, swimming across this nebula
浮遊感イカサマだ
The floating sensation is a fake
地に足つけ溶けていく naked
Naked, touching the ground and melting away
Hard days heartache again and again
擦り減って 傷付いて 悔しい涙でも
Frayed, wounded, even with tears of frustration
この痛みを消してワープして speed of light
Warping away this pain at the speed of light
行こう何光年先の果ての世界へ
Let's go to a world at the edge, light-years away
飛ばしてく 過剰に暴れたいね
Flying forward, wanting to rage excessively
くらおうさく響いたルール破って
Take that, breaking the loudly echoing rules
Double up かかって来いと笑うさ
Double up, I just smile and tell you to bring it on
四六時中 抱き合って あの惑星が消えるまで
Hugging each other 24/7 until that planet disappears
無重力サカサマ
Zero-gravity, upside-down
五線譜はみ出す lazy で tricky な trip さ
A lazy and tricky trip overflowing the staff
激しく奏でる月のレクイエム
A violently playing requiem of the moon
荷物などとうに捨てた 切符一つで
I discarded my luggage long ago, with just a single ticket
片道の non stop から“Utopia”
From a one-way non-stop to "Utopia"
鳴らし本能覚醒をここで証明しよう
Ring out, let's prove the awakening of instinct here
ブチあげる 不滅に 狂いたいね
Blow it up, immortal, I want to go crazy
つかみ怖いぐらいの衝撃 アタック脳天さ
Grab the terrifying impact, an attack straight to the head
Double up まだまだやれる なんてね
Double up, we can still do more, or so I say
今日も今日とて元気をお届けします
Delivering energy to you today as well!
パッパパパラパ パッパパパラパ
Pappara para pappara
三色昼寝付き 音をとりまえ
Three meals and a nap included, let's catch the sound
あと願わくば 褒めそねの でもしゃもーする
And ideally, praise and jealousy, but I'll do whatever
世界中の 愛をあげるよ
I'll give you all the love in the world
君にギュッ としてもらいます
I'll have you hug me tightly
君とずっと幸せを育てます
I'll cultivate happiness with you forever
急上昇 急上昇の急上昇の急上昇の
Rapidly rising, rapidly rising...
急ぎざかりのハイパーこそ猫である
A busy, hyper cat indeed
特別を君に背負うことを許可する
I allow you to carry something special
素直になれない 本音の尻尾を
Chasing the honest tail that can't be honest
追いかけて 優しく掴んでほしい
I want you to chase and gently catch it
構ってくれなきゃ寂しいにゃん
If you don't pay attention to me, I'll be lonely, nyan
他の子見てたらいけないにゃん
You mustn't look at other girls, nyan
人のこととか知らないにゃん
I don't care about other people, nyan
僕が一番可愛いらしいにゃん
I'm the cutest one of all, nyan
にゃんにゃん 君とずっとずっといたいので
Nyan-nyan, because I want to be with you forever and ever
僕に首を押しといてね
So put a collar around my neck
分かってないで そんなのなくたって
You don't get it, even without that
僕は君の運命のにゃんにゃん
I'm your destiny's nyan-nyan
夢が覚めてしまわぬように
So that the dream doesn't awaken
鈴の鳴る度高鳴ってね
Ringing the bell, making my heart beat faster
君の愛の全部をください
Please give me all of your love
そしたらずっとずっとにゃんにゃんしよう
Then let's do nyan-nyan forever and ever
なんて構って にゃんにゃん
How about paying attention to me, nyan-nyan?
みんな 今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming today!
あずきと一緒に にゃんにゃん声出していこう！
Let's raise our voices together with Azki, nyan-nyan!
行くよ！
Here we go!
アルファベットかませた奴らば当然当てるさ目指すは Omega
Those who flaunt their alphabet naturally aim for Omega
君と一対から果てまで Love だって
From being a pair with you to the end, it's love
オメガは猫マーク
Omega is the cat mark
臆病で迷いがちな小さなハートを
A cowardly and hesitant small heart
受け止めて両手で包んでほしい
I want you to catch it and wrap it in your hands
これでも愛情表現にゃ
Even so, this is an expression of affection, nyan
てかそれそろそろ気づいてにゃ
Or rather, hurry up and notice, nyan
人のこととか知らないにゃ
I don't care about other people, nyan
僕が一番大好きにゃ
I love you the most, nyan
にゃんにゃん 君とずっとずっといたいので
Nyan-nyan, because I want to be with you forever and ever
僕に首を押しといてね
So put a collar around my neck
分かってないで そんなのなくたって
You don't get it, even without that
僕は君の運命のにゃんにゃん
I'm your destiny's nyan-nyan
夢が覚めてしまわぬように
So that the dream doesn't awaken
鈴の鳴る度高鳴ってね
Ringing the bell, making my heart beat faster
君の愛の全部をください
Please give me all of your love
そしたらずっとずっとにゃんにゃんしよう
Then let's do nyan-nyan forever and ever
なんてかまって にゃんにゃん
How about paying attention to me, nyan-nyan?
もっとかまって にゃんにゃん
More attention, nyan-nyan!
にゃんにゃん にゃんにゃん
Nyan-nyan, nyan-nyan!
みんな 今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming today!
あずきと一緒に にゃんにゃん声出していこう！
Let's raise our voices together with Azki, nyan-nyan!
行くよ！
Here we go!
アルファベットかませた奴らば当然当てるさ目指すは Omega
Those who flaunt their alphabet naturally aim for Omega
君と一対から果てまで Love だって
From being a pair with you to the end, it's love
オメガは猫マーク
Omega is the cat mark
臆病で迷いがちな小さなハートを
A cowardly and hesitant small heart
受け止めて両手で包んでほしい
I want you to catch it and wrap it in your hands
これでも愛情表現にゃ
Even so, this is an expression of affection, nyan
てかそれそろそろ気づいてにゃ
Or rather, hurry up and notice, nyan
人のこととか知らないにゃ
I don't care about other people, nyan
僕が一番大好きにゃ
I love you the most, nyan
にゃんにゃん 君とずっとずっといたいので
Nyan-nyan, because I want to be with you forever and ever
僕に首を押しといてね
So put a collar around my neck
ディストピア to ソング・オブ・ザ・デッド！！
Dystopia song of the dead!!
振り出し ban! 番狂わせ
Throwing it out, turning the tables!
クラシックな暮らしにメタモルフォーゼ
Metamorphosis into a classic lifestyle
昔々そのまた昔
Long, long ago, once upon a time
ただ人類は食って眠って踊って笑ってた
Humans just ate, slept, danced, and laughed
キリのない苦痛 ギリギリの社会圧
Endless pain, edge-of-the-cliff social pressure
それが普通って映ってる朝のニュース
The morning news reflecting it as normal
また目が覚め強制ルーティン
Waking up again to a mandatory routine
朝食にバーガー 超常現象で現状一変
A burger for breakfast, current state upended by the supernatural
なんて夢見るオレ馬鹿？
Am I a fool for dreaming like that?
ソング・オブ・ザ・デッド！
Song of the dead!
i wanna! ダンシング ダンシング
I wanna! Dancing, dancing
ローリング ローリング
Rolling, rolling
オンリーワン マイライフ
Only one my life
やがて人生だって終わってしまうぜ
Sooner or later, life will come to an end
虚しさだけじゃ足りないだろ？
Emptiness alone isn't enough, is it?
ダンシング ダンシング
Dancing, dancing
ローリング ローリング 永遠だなんて
Rolling, rolling, saying it lasts forever
ありふれた幻想よりもいまを踊ろう
Let's dance in the present rather than a common illusion
エヴリナイト エヴリタイム
Every night, every time
遊び疲れるまで生きてみようぜ
Let's try living until we're tired of playing
映画さながら pan! パンデミック
Like in a movie, pan! Pandemic
阿鼻叫喚の共感症を割ってくモーゼ
Moses splitting the shrieking empathy syndrome
おかしい！ 可笑しい！？ いつの間にかゾンビ？
Weird! Funny!? Before I knew it, a zombie?
自身の尊厳を葬儀 リビングデッド行動
Burying one's own dignity, living dead actions
意味のないことを繰り返すだけの素行
Behavior that just repeats meaningless things
限りあるこのリアルを食い潰すなら
If we're going to devour this limited reality
一度足止め食らったっていいから脳内クリーニング
It's fine to be stopped for a moment, brain cleaning
君の人生はファストフードじゃないぜ
Your life isn't fast food
日々に増すシリアスを歌え
Sing of the seriousness increasing day by day
日々に増すラジカルを歌え
Sing of the radicalness increasing day by day
脳内乗り越えどんどんと壊せ
Overcome your mind and smash it more and more
クラシックな暮らしとメタモルフォーゼ
A classic lifestyle and metamorphosis
トゥインキー 食って生き残る？
Eat Twinkies and survive?
雰囲気飲んで生き終わる？ ah
Drink in the atmosphere and finish living? ah
ソング・オブ・ザ・デッド！
Song of the dead!
i wanna! ダンシング ダンシング
I wanna! Dancing, dancing
ローリング ローリング
Rolling, rolling
オンリーワン マイライフ
Only one my life
やがて人生だって終わってしまうぜ
Sooner or later, life will come to an end
虚しさだけじゃ足りないだろ？
Emptiness alone isn't enough, is it?
ダンシング ダンシング
Dancing, dancing
モーニング モーニング
Morning, morning
原点に立って新しいことを
Stand at the starting point and do something new
やりたいことをやろう
Let's do what we want to do
エヴリナイト エヴリタイム
Every night, every time
遊び疲れるまで生きてみようぜ
Let's try living until we're tired of playing
one, two, three, oh
ディストピア to ソング・オブ・ザ・デッド！！
Dystopia song of the dead!!
日々ひび増すシリアスを歌え
Sing of the seriousness increasing day by day
日々ひび増すラジカルを歌え
Sing of the radicalness increasing day by day
乗り越えどんどんと壊せ
Overcome and smash it more and more
クラシックな暮らしとメタモルフォーゼ
A classic lifestyle and metamorphosis
トゥインキー 食って生き残る？
Eat Twinkies and survive?
雰囲気飲んで生き終わる？
Drink in the atmosphere and finish living?
ソング・オブ・ザ・デッド！
Song of the dead!
i wanna! ダンシング ダンシング
I wanna! Dancing, dancing
ローリング ローリング
Rolling, rolling
オンリーワン マイライフ
Only one my life
やがて人生だって終わってしまうぜ
Sooner or later, life will come to an end
虚しさだけじゃ足りないだろ？
Emptiness alone isn't enough, is it?
ダンシング ダンシング
Dancing, dancing
モーニング モーニング
Morning, morning
原点に立って新しいことを
Stand at the starting point and do something new
やりたいことをやろう
Let's do what we want to do
エヴリナイト エヴリタイム
Every night, every time
遊び疲れるまで生きてみようぜ
Let's try living until we're tired of playing
i wanna! ダンシング ダンシング
I wanna! Dancing, dancing
ローリング ローリング
Rolling, rolling
オンリーワン マイライフ
Only one my life
やがて人生だって終わってしまうぜ
Sooner or later, life will come to an end
ディストピア to ソング・オブ・ザ・デッド！！
Dystopia song of the dead!!
あぁ あ ああ
Ah, ah, aa
言いかけた言葉を飲み込んで
Swallowing the words I almost said
あれっ 不具合かな ストップしちゃって
Huh? Is this a bug? It completely stopped
何も言わなくたってキミは
Even without saying anything, you
なんでもわかってくれるけど
Always understand everything, but
カッコつけてもつかなくて
Even when I try to look cool, it doesn't work out
失敗ばかりでごめんね
Sorry for always messing up
だけど言いたいことがあるよ
Yet, there's something I want to tell you
もうちょっと あとちょっと
Just a little more, just a bit more
強くNariたいな キミのためならね
I want to become stronger, if it's for you
ハートオンライン 気持ちまるごと
Heart Online, with all my feelings
乗せる電波 伝わるかな？
Riding the radio waves, will it reach you?
大好きだって 大切だって
That I love you, that you're precious
ホントはいつも言いたいのに
Even though I always want to say it for real
きっと ねぇ きっと 会えなくても
Surely, hey, surely even if we can't meet
キミとだから繋がれるよ
I can connect with you because it's you
ひらひらと舞う キミがくれた
Fluttering and dancing, what you gave me
ハートが集まって さくらになる
Gathers together into cherry blossoms
分岐ルートで戸惑うたび
Every time I hesitate at a branching route
正解なんてわからないけど
I don't know what the right answer is, but
一緒に探し当てた今日に
On this day we found together
だいすき すき すき よ すき
I love you so, so, so much!
すき すき すき よ すき
Love you, love you, love you so!
すき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
Love you so much, I love you!
もうぎゅっとぎゅっと手を握って
Hold my hands tightly, tightly,
ぎゅっとぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me close and tight,
ちゅってちゅってほっぺにしたい
Want a kiss, a kiss on the cheek,
ラビュ！
Love you!
だいすき すき すき よ すき...
Suki, suki, suki yo suki...
どっきどきなエブリデイ
A heart-pounding everyday,
更新してかなきゃイエスタデイ
Must update yesterday,
ハッピーエンドをよろしく
Wishing for a happy ending,
恋愛成就のキューピッド
Cupid of successful romance,
声も顔も全部いいんだもん
Voice and face, everything is great,
押しと引きのコンビネーション？
Push and pull combination?
無理よ 押すしかできない
Impossible, I can only push,
I love you ♡
だいすき すき すき よ すき
I love you so, so, so much!
すき すき すき よ すき
Love you, love you, love you so!
すき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
Love you so much, I love you!
もうぎゅっとぎゅっと手を握って
Hold my hands tightly, tightly,
ぎゅっとぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me close and tight,
ちゅってちゅってほっぺにしたい
Want a kiss, a kiss on the cheek,
ラビュ！
Love you!
大好き 大好き 止まらない
Love you, love you, can't stop,
目が合う瞬間 きゅんきゅんきゅん
The moment our eyes meet, my heart goes doki-doki,
（きゅんです！）
(It's a kyun!)
大好き 大好き 溢れちゃう
Love you, love you, it's overflowing,
だいすき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
I love you so, so, so much, love you!
（むげん だいすき！！！）
(Infinite love!!!)
（あいっ！）
(Love!)
攻略本なんてない
There's no walkthrough book,
だし激ムズ裏技もナッシング
No super hard cheat codes either,
七転び八起きで行くしかない
Can only go through trial and error,
散り積もでも
Even if it piles up,
あれもこれも考えたけど
Thought about this and that,
恋は常にインスピレーション
Love is always an inspiration,
勢いが大事でしょ
Momentum is important, right?
我爱你 ♡
I love you ♡
だいすき すき すき よ すき
I love you so, so, so much!
すき すき すき よ すき
Love you, love you, love you so!
すき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
Love you so much, I love you!
ねえ こっちこっち向いてよ baby
Hey, look this way, baby,
どっちどっち向いてんの baby
Which way are you looking, baby?
ずっとずっとこっち向いてよ ok？
Keep looking this way, ok?
こんなんじゅ こんなんじゅ 終わりない
Like this, like this, it never ends,
付き合いないと
If we're not dating,
ぴえんぴえんぴえん
Pien pien pien,
こんなんで こんなんで 終わらない
Like this, like this, it won't end,
だいすき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
I love you so, so, so much, love you!
だいすき すき すき よ すき
I love you so, so, so much!
すき すき すき よ すき
Love you, love you, love you so!
すき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
Love you so much, I love you!
もうぎゅっとぎゅっと手を握って
Hold my hands tightly, tightly,
ぎゅっとぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me close and tight,
ちゅってちゅってほっぺにしたい
Want a kiss, a kiss on the cheek,
ラビュ！
Love you!
大好き 大好き 止まらない
Love you, love you, can't stop,
目が合う瞬間 きゅんきゅんきゅん
The moment our eyes meet, my heart goes doki-doki,
（きゅんです！）
(It's a kyun!)
大好き 大好き 溢れちゃう
Love you, love you, it's overflowing,
だいすき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
I love you so, so, so much, love you!
（むげん だいすき！！！）
(Infinite love!!!)
（あいっ！）
(Love!)
ねぇねぇねぇねぇ盛り上がってくで
Hey hey hey, let's get hyped up!
猫も杓子もみんな大好きですか？
Does everyone, far and wide, love us?
（はーい！）
(Yes!)
（ありがとうございます！）
(Thank you very much!)
まだまだ盛り上がっていくだで！
Let's keep the excitement going!
だいすき すき すき よ すき
I love you so, so, so much!
すき すき すき よ すき
Love you, love you, love you so!
すき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
Love you so much, I love you!
もうぎゅっとぎゅっと手を握って
Hold my hands tightly, tightly,
ぎゅっとぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me close and tight,
ちゅってちゅってほっぺにしたい
Want a kiss, a kiss on the cheek,
ラビュ！
Love you!
大好き 大好き 止まらない
Love you, love you, can't stop,
目が合う瞬間 きゅんきゅんきゅん
The moment our eyes meet, my heart goes doki-doki,
（きゅんです！）
(It's a kyun!)
大好き 大好き 溢れちゃう
Love you, love you, it's overflowing,
だいすき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
I love you so, so, so much, love you!
（むげん だいすき！！！）
(Infinite love!!!)
（あいっ！）
(Love!)
だいすき すき すき よ すき
I love you so, so, so much!
すき すき すき よ すき
Love you, love you, love you so!
すき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
Love you so much, I love you!
もうぎゅっとぎゅっと手を握って
Hold my hands tightly, tightly,
ぎゅっとぎゅっと抱きしめて
Hold me close and tight,
ちゅってちゅってほっぺにしたい
Want a kiss, a kiss on the cheek,
ラビュ！
Love you!
大好き 大好き 止まらない
Love you, love you, can't stop,
目が合う瞬間 きゅんきゅんきゅん
The moment our eyes meet, my heart goes doki-doki,
（きゅんです！）
(It's a kyun!)
大好き 大好き 溢れちゃう
Love you, love you, it's overflowing,
だいすき すき すき よ すき よ ラビュ！
I love you so, so, so much, love you!
（むげん だいすき！！！）
(Infinite love!!!)
（あいっ！）
(Love!)
最後まで盛り上がりたかった人ー！
Anyone who wanted to get even more hyped until the very end?!
はーい！ありがとうございます！
Yes! Thank you!
ふぅー！お疲れ様でしたー！
Woo! Good work everyone!
おつみこさまでーす！
Otsumiko-sama!
皆さん、無限大好き、可愛かったですかー！？
Everyone, was "Mugen Daisuki" cute!?
可愛かったですかー！？
Was it cute!?
まだまだ声が小さいぞー！
Your voices are still too small!
もっともっといきますよー！無限大好き、可愛かったですかー！？
Let's go even more! Was "Mugen Daisuki" cute!?
大好きになっちゃいましたかー！？
Did you fall completely in love with us!?
もっともっと夢中になっちゃいましたかー！？
Did you get even more obsessed!?
いやぁ、楽しかったね。
Man, that was fun.
ついにみこさんもこんな大きなステージで...
And finally Miko-san on such a big stage...
立ってたねー！
You were standing there!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
爆笑問題じゃないことは、爆笑じゃないよね違うよね。
It's not Bakusho Mondai, right? Not Bakusho, right?
爆笑ではないよね、みこちゃん。
It's not "bakusho", Miko-chan.
せっかくMCやらしてもらえるということで、
Since we get to do the MC...
今日これねちょっとね、フロームのレスポンスやっていこうと思います。
We're gonna do some Q&A response things today.
みこさんもね、やりたいのあるって。
Miko-san also said she wanted to do one.
一体何なんですか？
What on earth is it?
みこさんのそのハニでね、エニートですかって。
Miko's "hani", is it "E-knit"?
聞いたらちょっと戻だったんですよ。
When I asked, it was a bit different.
そうだね、ハット戻だったね。
That's right, it was a hat knit.
でももう1個ね、新しく着たいことがあるんです。
But there's one more new thing I want to wear.
着たいこと？はい、何なに？
Want to wear? Yes, what is it?
みか、俺！
Mika, me!
恥ずかしいか！
How embarrassing!
それとも、気恥ずかしいか！
Or rather, is it bashful!
こと？違う！違う違う違う！
Huh? No! No, no, no!
まぁせっかくね、ステージ立ってるしね、
Well, since we're on stage,
そうね、そう！
that's right, yeah!
そうだね、みこ、おれ…って、みこさんが聞いたら、
That's right. When Miko asks, "Miko, my..."
会場のみんなが誇らしい恥ずかしい、どっちか叫んでください。
everyone in the venue, shout whether you're proud or embarrassed!
白上判断します！
Shirakami will judge!
え、ほんとにそんな、あ、聞き取れるのが大きい耳だから。
Eh, really? Well, with these big ears, I can hear everything.
そう！任せなさい！みんなの声聞きちゃうぞい！
That's right! Leave it to me! I'll hear everyone's voices!
え、じゃあいくよ、みんな大丈夫か？
Alright, here we go. Are you guys ready?
どうぞ！
Go ahead!
みこ！おれ…！
Miko! My...!
一歩先行くんだよ！
I'm going a step ahead!
それではいきます！
Here we go!
みこ！
Miko!
おれーー！
Myyy--!
なんかちょっと恥ずかしいだね 恥ずかしいね！
That's kind of embarrassing. It is embarrassing!
ぶさっ！
So cute!
ちょっとみこぴーの皆さん、ここは、みこさんがアイドルとして立ってる場所なんです！
MikoP everyone, this is the place where Miko stands as an idol!
もう一回行こうみこさん。もう一回、もう一回みんなもう一回、もっとお腹から声出して。
Let's do it again, Miko-san. One more time, push it from your belly.
じゃあ、みこが言う言葉に続けてください。
Now, repeat after the words Miko says.
続けるんかい。ちょっと待ってください。
Repeat after you? Wait a second.
なるほど。ええ？
I see. Eh?
いくよ！レペゼンAfter me！オーケー！オーケー！
Here we go! Represent After me! Okay! Okay!
いくよ！
Here we go!
みこーー！
Miko--!
おれーー！ おれーー！
My--! My--!
誇らしいよー！誇らしいよー！
You're so proud! You're so proud!
これはもう万丈一致誇らしいだよ！
This is unanimously something to be proud of!
誇らしい。ちょっともう一回行く、もう一回行く、行く行く！みこ！みこ！おれーー！
Proud. Let's do it again! Miko! Miko! Myyy--!
おれーー！
Myyy--!
誇らしいよー！
You're so proud!
素晴らしいー！
Wonderful!
じゃあちょっと白上もいいですか？
Then, can Shirakami go next?
あ、いいですよ。
Oh, sure.
白上もね、今日来てくれてるスコーナーみんなに改めて聞きたいことがありますよ！
Shirakami also has something to ask all the Scorers who came today!
なんですか？
What is it?
じゃあね、白上が、白上のこと何万回愛してるって言ったらみんな答えてください！いいですか？
Well then, when Shirakami says how many tens of thousands of times she loves Shirakami, everyone answer!
いいですかー？
Is that okay?
いいですごーい！
Yes, awesome!
じゃあ、言っちゃいますよ！
Alright, I'm gonna say it!
スコーナーみんな、白上のこと何万回愛してる？
Scorers everyone, how many tens of thousands of times do you love Shirakami?
100万回！
One million times!
ありがとう、じゃあもっと声出せるよねみんな。白上のこと何万回愛してますか？
Thank you. Then you can make your voices even louder, right? How many times do you love Shirakami?
100万回！愛してるー！
One million times! I love you!
気持ちすぎ！手遅れ！気持ちすぎだー！
Too emotional! Too late! Too emotional!
あとね、あとね、なんかライブと言ったらウェーブですよ。
Also, speaking of live concerts, it's the wave.
え？ ウェーブやっていいんですか？
Eh? Can we do the wave?
そう、だけど、なんかさ、横からはあったけどさ、前から後ろなかったじゃん。
Yeah, but we've had it from side to side, but not from front to back.
え、できる？みんな。できる？
Eh, can you do it? Everyone. Can you?
いいの？
Is it okay?
お、いける！見てみたい！見てみたい！
Oh, we can do it! I want to see it! I want to see it!
じゃあ、ちょっと前の人からわーーってやったら、ちょっと椅子に座っちゃおうか。椅子に座ろう。
So, if the front people do Waaah, then let's sit in chairs. Let's sit in chairs.
そうね。そうそうそう、ずっと立ちっぱもなんなので、なのでまずまず立っててね、まず立ってて。
Right. Standing the whole time is a lot, so first of all, stand up, stand up first.
あ、みんな立って。そうそうそうきっかけどうする？
Ah, everyone stand. How should we trigger it?
え、なんか、ピタって。
Eh, like, perfectly.
あ、じゃあ。
Ah, then.
ね、猫耳長女。
Cat-ears eldest sister.
ふぶみこさん。
Fubumiko-san.
ふ、ふみこさんだろ。あ、ふぶみこさん。
Fumiko-san right? Ah, Fubumiko-san.
大好きピー！
Daisuki P!
大好きピー！ってやったら前の人からわーーで、で、座ってで後ろの人がわーーってやって座る。わあ！
When you do that, the front people go Waaah, sit down, and the back people go Waaah and sit. Waaah!
できますか？
Can you do it?
できるよな！できるよな！
You can do it! You can do it!
ちょっとみなさんの団結した姿見せてください！いいよー！
Show us everyone's united form! Alright!
じゃあ、いきますよ、みこさん。はい。
Well then, here we go, Miko-san. Yes.
ふぶみこさん！
Fubumiko-san!
大好きピー！
Daisuki P!
これがふぶみこさんの波動、波動が、波動が後ろまで！すっごい！すっごい！すっごい！
This is Fubumiko's wave, going all the way to the back! Amazing! Amazing!
ええ、きれい！みんなありがとうー！
Beautiful! Thank you everyone!
やばい。
Awesome.
ということでですね、では、自己紹介もしてなかったけど、ま、きでもお願いしましただったのいで。
With that said, we hadn't done our self-introductions yet, but since we asked Maki to do it...
あ、はい。はい。じゃあね、巻いていきましょうかね。
Ah, yes. Well then, let's wrap things up.
はい、実はですね、韓国インドネシアでライブビューイング中です！みなさん観てますか？観てますか？
Actually, we're having a live viewing in Korea and Indonesia! Are you watching?
配信のみんなも観てください！ふうー！
Everyone watching the stream, please watch too! Woo!
そしてそして？
And then?
はい、え、ライブの感想をハッシュタグ「ホロライブフェスEXPO24_アンダーペイトゥ」でSNSにアップしてください！
Please upload your live concert impressions to SNS with the hashtag!
お願いしまーーす！
Please do!
そしてさっきのことに、え？
And about that earlier thing, eh?
無料パートはここまでです！
The free part ends here!
やだやだやだ！もっと見たい！もっと見たいっしょ！どうすればいいんだい？みこさん。
No way! I want to see more! What should we do, Miko-san?
それは、みなさん、チケットを買うんだ！わーー！買ってくれー！
That is, everyone, buy tickets! Waaah! Please buy them!
みんなも買ってって言った！
Everyone said buy them too!
え、買って！
Eh, buy them!
買った！今度では、かん、みんな、ふぶみこ！
Bought! Next, um, everyone, Fubumiko!
いい声だよ！もっと！
Good voice! More!
買ったよー！
We bought them!
よし！
Alright!
じゃあ最後にもう一回コールして、みんな、このあとのねメンバーにもっと気をつけるように、エンジかけるよ！
Then lastly, let's do a call one more time to pump up the members coming up next!
話を聞いた? 立ちましょう皆さん!
Did you hear that? Everyone, stand up!
あぁ～ さぁ～
Ah~ Now~
立って立ってみんな立って立って!
Stand, stand, everyone stand, stand!
じゃあふぶきさんが「すき」って言ったら、「すき」って返してもらう。
Then, if Fubuki-san says "Suki", you reply with "Suki".
え?
Eh?
いいじゃん！いいじゃん！
It's fine! It's fine!
じゃあいきますよ せーの 「すきー!」
Then here we go, ready, set, "Suki!"
もっと! 「すきー!」
More! "Suki!"
「すきー!」
"Suki!"
ちょっともっと！やるぞー！ 「すきー!」
Wait, even more! Let's do this! "Suki!"
最後！ だーいすきー! だーいすきー!
Last one! Super suki! Super suki!
はい、せーの!
Ready, set!
キャプチャー・ザ・モーメント!
Capture the Moment!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended! Thank you for watching!
あの涙が今の僕らを繋いで
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから 一人じゃないから
Because a piece of you is in this heart, I am not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Within the words I drew someday,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
The colored scenery swayed beyond my closed eyes.
少し戸惑う風の中
In the slightly bewildering wind,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping flower petals, our voices.
一瞬 一瞬 捕らえるみたいに
As if capturing every single moment,
もっと もっと 踏み出せたら
If we can step forward even more...
あの涙が今の僕らを繋いで
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
Because a piece of you is in this heart.
強くなってもいい 今の光を
It's okay if we aren't strong, let's gather
僕と 集め 空に放つ
The current light with you into the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから
We will gently make this miracle shine together,
力が湧くから
Because it gives us strength.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clutching new seeds tightly,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
I sowed them with strong wishes for a distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては
Letting the winds of hope blow,
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
Petals of ideals, praying for tomorrow's sky.
何百 億も 輝く星みたいに
Like hundreds of millions of shining stars,
ずっと ずっと 終わらないから
It will never, ever end.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile firmly embraces the past,
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
As I reach out my hands toward the future now.
時に転んでも 空を見上げよう
Even if we stumble sometimes, let's look up at the sky.
笑い 日々を 刻んでいく
Engraving the days we laughed...
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから
Promising to seize the next dream,
この手で踏み出そう ここから
Let's step forward with these hands, from right here.